how to claim Manulife travel insurance
Manulife bank is a Canadian online bank
offering savings accounts mortgages and
other financial services without
traditional branches customers access
their accounts through online banking
mobile apps and ATMs first go to Google
and search Manulife GM travel portal
then click on first link then click on
start a new claim then select which
insurance type are you claiming under
Group insurance or individual insurance
then select your type of claim select
trip
cancellation on this page click on no
then select reason for cancelling after
that answer the following
questions then click let's get
started here fill up all the insurance
related question
after that submit your
claim that's it thanks for watching